Why do I feel lost
after she left?
After a successful hunt,
ancient humans needed a brief rest.
But prolonged relaxation
was detrimental to survival.
Modern humans retained this mechanism.
After achieving a goal,
the brain uses a sense of emptiness
to urge you to seek new challenges,
ensuring continuous adaptation to the environment.
What is the feeling of love?
When you think of the other person,
the brain's ventral tegmental area
and nucleus accumbens
release dopamine,
triggering excitement,
craving, and motivation.
It's similar to an addiction mechanism.
Physical contact like hugging
or holding hands
triggers these attachment hormones,
bringing a sense of security and trust.
This is especially evident in long-term relationships.
You involuntarily
pay attention to their every move,
even affecting your daily decisions.
She doesn't affect my decisions that much.
Don't mess with me.
That's not it.
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
Hello?
One of the company's top livestreaming rooms got banned.
You guys decide on your own.
Don't call me unless it's important.
This is an urgent matter!
Even affecting daily decisions.
Wen Pei'an.
What does she want?
This aggressive aura...
Could it be...
This...
is our
Contractual Couple
Cooperation Termination Agreement.
Take a look.
If there are no issues,
then sign it.
It's time to end this.
It seems
she can't wait
to terminate the agreement with me.
I was just being sentimental.
Wait a minute.
Aren't you going to carefully
check the amount on here
before signing? No issues?
No need.
I'll transfer it to you today.
Thanks.
Pleasure doing business.
What's wrong?
Is there something else?
Remember,
expense claims need receipts attached.
The cooperation is finally over.
I should be happy, right?
This project is already finished.
Why does my heart feel
so empty?
I couldn't really have...
Assistant!
Question.
After a project ends,
why does one feel empty inside?
Why is that?
During the project,
goals were clear,
tasks were defined. After completion, you lose direction,
easily leading to a sense of emptiness.
Right.
During the project process,
you invest a lot of emotion and energy.
After it ends,
that emotion has nowhere to go,
causing an emotional disparity.
Normal.
These are all normal psychological effects.
It'll pass.
This...
What is this?
Don't scare me.
How to detach from this emotional state?
Minimize unnecessary private communication.
Strictly limit conversations to work topics.
If possible,
reduce opportunities to meet them.
Choose open office environments,
avoid contact in enclosed spaces.
Detachment is a gradual process.
It requires time and patience.
Allow yourself occasional emotional relapses.
Gradually move past the emotional distress,
and return to a rational work and life state.
There's something I need to report to you.
Can't you see I'm busy?
It's about Xin Tong.
I'm free now.
Speak.
I just now
saw in the system
her resignation report.
What did you say?
Xin Tong!
Hello?
What's wrong?
Why didn't you say anything about moving out?
Our current contract
is already over.
It wouldn't be appropriate
for me to keep living at your place.
Why are you resigning?
Because
someone offered me a high salary to poach me.
I'm a bit uncomfortable without you here.
You'll get used to it soon.
He's just developed a temporary dependency
because of this cooperation.
I need to help the client with withdrawal.
That's my professional integrity.
Withdrawal.
Withdrawal is so hard.
If,
by twelve o'clock,
you call me one more time,
then I'll definitely answer.
Hello?
I like you.